(Transcribed by TurboScribe. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) The fifth graders at Kennedy School had a
science fair.
They had to work in teams of three.
Each group had to come up with a
project.
They were to make a display.
They had one month to work on their
projects.
The best project would get a medal and
ribbons.
On the day of the science fair, everyone
brought their projects.
There were simple ones.
There were complicated ones.
Some people studied plants and animals.
Some looked into electricity and magnetism.
Some even did projects on bacteria and viruses.
All the projects were good.
It made picking the winner very difficult.